Contact

srhsatx@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarahhumme-dnp-rn-nea-bccenp-395646b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Physician Relations
Patient Safety
Acute Care

Sarah Humme, DNP, RN, NEA-BC, CENP

Chief Nursing Officer/Chief Operating Officer at Southwest General Hospital San Antonio, TX

San Antonio, Texas

Summary

Experienced Chief Nursing Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Medicine, Physician Relations, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Healthcare, and Patient Safety. Strong research professional with a Doctor of Nursing Practice focused in Executive Leadership from Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center.

Experience

IASIS HEALTHCARE CORPORATION
Chief Nursing Informatics Officer, Cerner Millenium Project
August 2016 - Present (4 years)

Franklin, Tennessee

Southwest General Hospital San Antonio, TX Chief Nursing Officer/Chief Operating Officer February 2012 - August 2016 (4 years 7 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Methodist Texsan Hospital
Chief Nursing Officer
January 2011 - January 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Methodist Healthcare System
VIce President of Nursing Practice and Patient Safery
May 2008 - January 2011 (2 years 9 months)

Northeast Baptist Hospital Director of Surgical Services 2004 - 2008 (4 years)

Education

Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Executive Leadership · (2010 - 2012)

Yale University
Master of Science, Nursing · (1979 - 1981)

BSN Northeastern University Boston MA Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (1970 - 1975)